
--- Inspecting: SATURDAY PROVOST DAILY REPORT  (School Template).docx ---
Paragraphs:
1: DAILY REPORT
2: ò Date û (Day and date e.g Friday, 12/05/2035)
3:  ò Sub-Unit: Protocol
4:  ò Prepared by: 
5:  ò Submitted to: Protocol Head, Hospitality Unit
7:  REPORT DETAILS
8: Attendance Summary (Day, Date e.g Friday, 23/07/2035)
10: General Meeting
11: Male:
12: Female:
13: Total:
15: Chaplaincy Meeting
16: Male:
17: Female:
18: Total:
20: CHOP
21: Male:
22: Female:
23: Total:
25: WORD FEAST
26: Male:
27: Female:
28: Total:
33: Service Overview
34: (Briefly describe the overall flow of the service unit during this pre-service and inside the service, including performance of protocol members on duty.) 
35: Example; (The service was running smoothly, but there was a bit of a challenge with tag collection after the service was over)
37: Challenges & Incidents
38: (List any obstacles faced during subunit duties or specific incidents in the pre-service and service that required attention.)
40: Workflow Suggestions
41: (Based on todayÆs experience, what could be improved for next time?)

Tables:

--- Inspecting: SUN-TUE-THUR PROVOST DAILY REPORT  (School Template).docx ---
Paragraphs:
1: DAILY REPORT
2: ò Date û (THURSDAY 5TH FEBRUARY 2026) 02/05/2026
3:  ò Sub-Unit: Protocol
4:  ò Prepared by: ONYEACHONAM BUCHI BENEDICT
5:  ò Submitted to: Protocol Head, Hospitality Unit
7:  REPORT DETAILS
8: Attendance Summary (THURSDAY 5TH FEBRUARY 2026) 02/05/2026
9: Male: 31
10: Female: 60
11: Total: 91
13: Service Overview
1. Hospitality members, especially on Thursday Preservice tend to show up to preservice towards the last 10 or 15 minutes, meaning majority either miss prayers or worship and only get bits and parts of the charge. 
2. Hospitality members again, especially on Thursday Preservice tend to lack intentionality as regards prayers and the charge, I observed this as the prayers went on most members would rather be lost in activities elsewhere or during the charge be absent-minded. 
3. The Service itself was a bit chaotic as the issues of no seat is still clear, some hospitality members posted to serve could not have the place to serve as the USHERS had given out our seat even when we were still in pre-service for those without seat covers and for some without. 

15: Challenges & Incidents
16: Posting Issues: None of the Assigned Protocol members for (i)Entrance Allocation: Oreoluwa (ii)Tag Allocation: Matthew (iii)Counting during service: vanessachukwu 
17: (iv)Tag Collection: Kosisochukwu_Igbokwe ,  RúJOICú were available on time to carry out their duties today understandable partially due to no internet but not so much as it is not a valid reason for coming late to preservice as a whole , with that understanding, I replaced OREOLUWA with VICTORIA GEORGE for the Entrance Allocation, I replaced MATTHEW with OLAOYE PROSPER, I replaced VANESSACHUKWU with OKAFOR PETER , I replaced REJOICE and reassigned MATTHEW to collect tags and also retained KOSI for tag collection as well. 

18: Hospitality in Service: In this service, I saw Hospitality members bring anything and everything to Gentleness 03, without even praying for them, GT 03 became unnecessarily crowded and at some point, couldnÆt even differentiate between who was sick and who wasnÆt. 

19: GT 03: GT 03 is always packed up but today, we fought to ensure space was kept, so that sick people actually have space to breathe, but then student council member oseaghe came and forcefully put 4 boys at gentleness 03, when Victoria George tried to reason with her, she acted in a manner not  worthy to be typed in this document. We had to live with a very congested GT 03, and it didnÆt improve the conditions of those under the weather. 

20: Attendance :  Attendance always never comes for ALTAR PEACE, ALTER LEFT , ALTAR RIGHT, and we must run around with the posting book after service to rectify which in the long run may want to prevent people from serving in those place during Thursday services. 

22: Workflow Suggestions
23: In my opinion I openly suggest that we 
1. Have an understanding with both ushering and Student council officials and Attendance unit for better flow of operations in service. 
24: For ushers: To protect the hospitality seat on every elevation as it is the seat directly in front of them.
25: For Student Council: To ensure there is more clarity on why we need the entirety of the last row in gentleness to avoid issues. Especially on Thursday and Saturdays. 
26: For Attendance unit: To please give attendance to hospitality unit members at Altar Left, Altar Right and Altar Peace especially for Thursday Services as weÆre still students and would need the attendances
27: 2. Endeavor Hospitality members to be early for preservice, protocol members should also be early for services even if theyÆve not been assigned for something.

Tables:

--- Inspecting: WED-FRI  PROVOST DAILY REPORT  (School Template).docx ---
Paragraphs:
1: DAILY REPORT
2: ò Date û (Day and date e.g. Friday, 12/05/2035)
3:  ò Sub-Unit: Protocol
4:  ò Prepared by: 
5:  ò Submitted to: Protocol Head, Hospitality Unit
7:  REPORT DETAILS
8: Attendance Summary (Day, Date e.g. Friday, 23/07/2035)

12: Male:
13: Female:
14: Total:
16: Service Overview
17: (Briefly describe the overall flow of the service unit during this pre-service and inside the service, including performance of protocol members on duty.) 
18: Example; (The service was running smoothly, but there was a bit of a challenge with tag collection after the service was over)
20: Challenges & Incidents
21: (List any obstacles faced during subunit duties or specific incidents in the pre-service and service that required attention.)
23: Workflow Suggestions
24: (Based on todayÆs experience, what could be improved for next time?)

Tables:
